A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, Grants, SG 1, Series 18 FA290
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Grants, 3; 55.44 Cubic Feet
  - Hunter College, Research Foundation of the City University of New York - Career Explorations 83 - A New York City Summer Youth Employment and Career Planning Program (Part One) - Donna E. Shalala and Diane H. DePuydt, 1983-1985 (Box 64, Folder 464)
  - Hunter College, Research Foundation of the City University of New York - Career Explorations 83 - A New York City Summer Youth Employment and Career Planning Program (Part One) - Donna E. Shalala and Diane H. DePuydt, 1983-1985 (Box 64, Folder 465)
  - Hunter College, Research Foundation of the City University of New York - Career Explorations 83 - A New York City Summer Youth Employment and Career Planning Program (Part Two) - Donna E. Shalala and Diane H. DePuydt, May-September, 1983 (Box 64, Folder 466)
  - Hunter College, Research Foundation of the City University of New York - Career Explorations 83 - A New York City Summer Youth Employment and Career Planning Program (Part Two) - Donna E. Shalala and Diane H. DePuydt, May-September, 1983 (Box 64, Folder 467)
  - Hunter College, Research Foundation of the City University of New York - Career Explorations 84 - A New York City Summer Youth Employment and Career Planning Program - Donna E. Shalala and Nicholas Freudenberg, 1984-1985 (Box 64, Folder 468)
  - Hunter College, Research Foundation of the City University of New York - Career Explorations 84 - A New York City Summer Youth Employment and Career Planning Program - Donna E. Shalala and Nicholas Freudenberg, 1984-1985 (Box 64, Folder 469)
  - Hunter College, Research Foundation of the City University of New York - Career Explorations 84 - A New York City Summer Youth Employment and Career Planning Program - Donna E. Shalala and Nicholas Freudenberg, 1984-1985 (Box 64, Folder 470)
  - Hunter College, Research Foundation of the City University of New York - Career Explorations 85 - A New York City Summer Youth Employment and Career Planning Program - Donna E. Shalala and Nicholas Freudenberg, 1984-1986 (Box 64, Folder 471)
  - Hunter College, Research Foundation of the City University of New York - Career Explorations 85 - A New York City Summer Youth Employment and Career Planning Program - Donna E. Shalala and Nicholas Freudenberg, 1984-1986 (Box 65, Folder 472)
  - Hunter College, Research Foundation of the City University of New York - Career Explorations 85 - A New York City Summer Youth Employment and Career Planning Program - Donna E. Shalala and Nicholas Freudenberg, 1984-1986 (Box 65, Folder 473)
  - Hunter College, Research Foundation of the City University of New York - Career Explorations 85 - A New York City Summer Youth Employment and Career Planning Program - Donna E. Shalala and Nicholas Freudenberg, 1984-1986 (Box 65, Folder 474)
  - Independent Sector - Annual Membership Dues - Brian O'Connell, April-October, 1982 (Box 65, Folder 475)
  - Independent Sector - Annual Membership Dues - Brian O'Connell, April-October, 1982 (Box 65, Folder 476)
  - Independent Sector - Educational Materials on the Role of U.S. Voluntary Organizations and Philanthropy - Brian O'Connell, 1982-1984 (Box 65, Folder 477)
  - Independent Sector - Educational Materials on the Role of U.S. Voluntary Organizations and Philanthropy - Brian O'Connell, 1982-1984 (Box 65, Folder 478)
  - Independent Sector - Educational Materials on the Role of U.S. Voluntary Organizations and Philanthropy - Brian O'Connell, 1982-1984 (Box 65, Folder 479)
  - Independent Sector - General Support - Brian O'Connell, 1983-1984 (Box 65, Folder 480)
  - Independent Sector - General Support - Brian O'Connell, 1983-1984 (Box 65, Folder 481)
  - Independent Sector - Strengthening the Role of Private Sector Leadership in America - John Gardner, 1983-1989 (Box 65, Folder 482)
  - Independent Sector - Strengthening the Role of Private Sector Leadership in America - John Gardner, 1983-1989 (Box 65, Folder 483)
  - Independent Sector - Strengthening the Role of Private Sector Leadership in America - John Gardner, 1983-1989 (Box 66, Folder 484)
  - Independent Sector - General Support - Brian O'Connell, 1984 (Box 66, Folder 485)
  - Independent Sector - General Support - Brian O'Connell, February-October, 1984 (Box 66, Folder 486)
  - Independent Sector - General Support - Brian O'Connell, 1985-1986 (Box 66, Folder 487)
  - Independent Sector - General Support - Brian O'Connell, 1985-1986 (Box 66, Folder 488)
  - Institute of International Education (IIE) - Special Services in International Educational Exchange - Walter B. Edgerton, 1982-1986 (Box 66, Folder 489)
  - Institute of International Education (IIE) - Special Services in International Educational Exchange - Walter B. Edgerton, 1982-1986 (Box 66, Folder 490)
  - Institute of International Education (IIE) - Special Services in International Educational Exchange - Walter B. Edgerton, 1982-1986 (Box 66, Folder 491)
  - Institute of Society, Ethics and Life Sciences (The Hastings Center) (ISEFS) - President's Commission for the Study of Ethical Problems in Medicine and Biomedical and Behavioral Research, Support of Eight President's Commission Commonwealth Fellows - Alexander Capron, 1980-1983 (Box 66, Folder 492)
  - Institute of Society, Ethics and Life Sciences (The Hastings Center) (ISEFS) - President's Commission for the Study of Ethical Problems in Medicine and Biomedical and Behavioral Research, Support of Eight President's Commission Commonwealth Fellows - Alexander Capron, 1980-1983 (Box 67, Folder 493)
  - Institute of Society, Ethics and Life Sciences (The Hastings Center) (ISEFS) - President's Commission for the Study of Ethical Problems in Medicine and Biomedical and Behavioral Research, Support of Eight President's Commission Commonwealth Fellows - Alexander Capron, 1980-1983 (Box 67, Folder 494)
  - International Study Group of the International Association for Adolescent Psychiatry and Allied Professions (IACAP) - Travel and Living Expenses Connected with Meetings in Stockholm and Nigeria and for Costs of Proposed Book on Conference Theme - "Children in Turmoil: Tomorrow's Parents" - Albert J. Solnit, 1980-1983 (Box 67, Folder 495)
  - International Study Group of the International Association for Adolescent Psychiatry and Allied Professions (IACAP) - Travel and Living Expenses Connected with Meetings in Stockholm and Nigeria and for Costs of Proposed Book on Conference Theme - "Children in Turmoil: Tomorrow's Parents" - Albert J. Solnit, 1980-1983 (Box 67, Folder 496)
  - International Study Group of the International Association for Adolescent Psychiatry and Allied Professions (IACAP) - Travel and Living Expenses Connected with Meetings in Stockholm and Nigeria and for Costs of Proposed Book on Conference Theme - "Children in Turmoil: Tomorrow's Parents" - Albert J. Solnit, 1980-1983 (Box 67, Folder 497)
  - International Study Group of the International Association for Adolescent Psychiatry and Allied Professions (IACAP) - Travel and Living Expenses Connected with Meetings in Stockholm and Nigeria and for Costs of Proposed Book on Conference Theme - "Children in Turmoil: Tomorrow's Parents" - Albert J. Solnit, 1980-1983 (Box 67, Folder 498)
  - International Center for Integrative Studies (The Door - A Center for Alternatives) (ICIS) - Evaluating Social and Medical Services to Troubled Youth - Charles D. Terry, 1980-1984 (Box 67, Folder 499)
  - International Center for Integrative Studies (The Door - A Center for Alternatives) (ICIS) - Evaluating Social and Medical Services to Troubled Youth - Charles D. Terry, 1980-1984 (Box 68, Folder 500)
  - International Center for Integrative Studies (The Door - A Center for Alternatives) (ICIS) - Evaluating Social and Medical Services to Troubled Youth - Charles D. Terry, 1980-1984 (Box 68, Folder 501)
  - International Center for Integrative Studies (The Door - A Center for Alternatives) (ICIS) - Evaluating Social and Medical Services to Troubled Youth - Charles D. Terry, 1980-1984 (Box 68, Folder 502)
  - International Women's Health Coalition (IWHC) - A Funding Source for Women's Health Programs in Developing Countries - Joan B. Dunlop, 1984-1986 (Box 68, Folder 503)
  - International Women's Health Coalition (IWHC) - A Funding Source for Women's Health Programs in Developing Countries - Joan B. Dunlop, 1984-1986 (Box 68, Folder 504)
  - International Women's Health Coalition (IWHC) - A Funding Source for Women's Health Programs in Developing Countries - Joan B. Dunlop, 1984-1986 (Box 68, Folder 505)
  - University of Iowa - Developing A Comprehensive System of Publicly Supported Health Care Services for Mothers and Children in Iowa - Samuel Levey and John W. Colloton, 1982-1985 (Box 68, Folder 506)
  - University of Iowa - Developing A Comprehensive System of Publicly Supported Health Care Services for Mothers and Children in Iowa - Samuel Levey and John W. Colloton, 1982-1985 (Box 69, Folder 507)
  - University of Iowa - Developing A Comprehensive System of Publicly Supported Health Care Services for Mothers and Children in Iowa - Samuel Levey and John W. Colloton, 1982-1985 (Box 69, Folder 508)
  - University of Iowa - Developing A Comprehensive System of Publicly Supported Health Care Services for Mothers and Children in Iowa - Samuel Levey and John W. Colloton, 1982-1985 (Box 69, Folder 509)
  - University of Iowa - Developing A Comprehensive System of Publicly Supported Health Care Services for Mothers and Children in Iowa - Samuel Levey and John W. Colloton, 1982-1985 (Box 69, Folder 510)
  - University of Iowa - Developing A Comprehensive System of Publicly Supported Health Care Services for Mothers and Children in Iowa - Samuel Levey and John W. Colloton, 1982-1985 (Box 69, Folder 511)
  - University of Iowa - Developing A Comprehensive System of Publicly Supported Health Care Services for Mothers and Children in Iowa - Samuel Levey and John W. Colloton, 1982-1985 (Box 69, Folder 512)
  - University of Iowa - Developing A Comprehensive System of Publicly Supported Health Care Services for Mothers and Children in Iowa - Samuel Levey and John W. Colloton, 1982-1985 (Box 70, Folder 513)
  - University of Iowa - Executive Nurse Leadership Program to Improve the Management Skills of Nurses with Top Executive Potential - Marilyn T. Molen, 1983-1987 (Box 70, Folder 514)
  - University of Iowa - Executive Nurse Leadership Program to Improve the Management Skills of Nurses with Top Executive Potential - Marilyn T. Molen, 1983-1987 (Box 70, Folder 515)
  - University of Iowa - Executive Nurse Leadership Program to Improve the Management Skills of Nurses with Top Executive Potential - Marilyn T. Molen, 1983-1987 (Box 70, Folder 516)
  - University of Iowa - Executive Nurse Leadership Program (Phase Two) - Marilyn T. Molen, 1983-1984 (Box 70, Folder 517)
  - University of Iowa - Executive Nurse Leadership Program (Phase Two) - Marilyn T. Molen, 1983-1984 (Box 70, Folder 518)
  - Johns Hopkins Hospital - Strengthening the Fund's Program for Academic Health Centers - Robert M. Heyssel, 1982-1983 (Box 71, Folder 519)
  - Johns Hopkins Hospital - Strengthening the Fund's Program for Academic Health Centers - Robert M. Heyssel, 1982-1983 (Box 71, Folder 520)
  - Johns Hopkins Hospital - The Commonwealth Fund Task Force on Academic Health Centers - Robert M. Heyssel, 1982-1984 (Box 71, Folder 521)
  - Johns Hopkins Hospital - The Commonwealth Fund Task Force on Academic Health Centers - Robert M. Heyssel, 1982-1984 (Box 71, Folder 522)
  - Johns Hopkins Hospital - The Commonwealth Fund Task Force on Academic Health Centers - Robert M. Heyssel, 1982-1984 (Box 71, Folder 523)
  - Johns Hopkins Hospital - Program of Reports - Task Force on Academic Health Centers - Robert M. Heyssel, 1983-1987 (Box 72, Folder 524)
  - Johns Hopkins Hospital - Program of Reports - Task Force on Academic Health Centers - Robert M. Heyssel, 1983-1987 (Box 72, Folder 525)
  - Johns Hopkins Hospital - Program of Reports - Task Force on Academic Health Centers - Robert M. Heyssel, 1983-1987 (Box 72, Folder 526)
  - Johns Hopkins Hospital - Program of Reports - Task Force on Academic Health Centers - Robert M. Heyssel, 1983-1987 (Box 72, Folder 527)
  - Johns Hopkins Hospital - Program of Reports - Task Force on Academic Health Centers - Robert M. Heyssel, 1983-1987 (Box 72, Folder 528)
  - Johns Hopkins Hospital - Program of Reports - Task Force on Academic Health Centers - Robert M. Heyssel, 1983-1987 (Box 72, Folder 529)
  - Johns Hopkins Hospital - Program of Reports - The Commonwealth Fund Task Force on Academic Health Centers, 1984-1985 - Robert M. Heyssel, May-November, 1984 (Box 73, Folder 530)
  - Johns Hopkins Hospital - Program of Reports - The Commonwealth Fund Task Force on Academic Health Centers, 1984-1985 - Robert M. Heyssel, May-November, 1984 (Box 73, Folder 531)
  - Johns Hopkins Hospital - Program of Reports - The Commonwealth Fund Task Force on Academic Health Centers (Part Two) - Robert M. Heyssel, 1984-1985 (Box 73, Folder 532)
  - Johns Hopkins Hospital - Program of Reports - The Commonwealth Fund Task Force on Academic Health Centers (Part Two) - Robert M. Heyssel, 1984-1985 (Box 73, Folder 533)
  - Johns Hopkins Hospital - Program of Reports - The Commonwealth Fund Task Force on Academic Health Centers (Part Three) - Robert M. Heyssel, 1984-1988 (Box 73, Folder 534)
  - Johns Hopkins Hospital - Program of Reports - The Commonwealth Fund Task Force on Academic Health Centers (Part Three) - Robert M. Heyssel, 1984-1988 (Box 73, Folder 535)
  - Johns Hopkins Hospital - Program of Reports - The Commonwealth Fund Task Force on Academic Health Centers (Part Three) - Robert M. Heyssel, 1984-1988 (Box 73, Folder 536)
  - Johns Hopkins Hospital - Program of Reports - The Commonwealth Fund Task Force on Academic Health Centers (Part Three) - Robert M. Heyssel, 1984-1988 (Box 73, Folder 537)
  - Johns Hopkins Hospital - Program of Reports - The Commonwealth Fund Task Force on Academic Health Centers (Part Three) - Robert M. Heyssel, 1984-1988 (Box 74, Folder 538)
  - Johns Hopkins Hospital - Program of Reports - The Commonwealth Fund Task Force on Academic Health Centers (Part Four) - Robert M. Heyssel, 1985-1987 (Box 74, Folder 539)
  - Johns Hopkins Hospital - Program of Reports - The Commonwealth Fund Task Force on Academic Health Centers (Part Four) - Robert M. Heyssel, 1985-1987 (Box 74, Folder 540)
  - Johns Hopkins Hospital - Program of Reports - The Commonwealth Fund Task Force on Academic Health Centers (Part Four) - Robert M. Heyssel, 1985-1987 (Box 74, Folder 541)
  - Johns Hopkins Hospital - Program of Reports - The Commonwealth Fund Task Force on Academic Health Centers (Part Four) - Robert M. Heyssel, 1985-1987 (Box 74, Folder 542)
  - Johns Hopkins Hospital - Program of Reports - The Commonwealth Fund Task Force on Academic Health Centers (Part Four) - Robert M. Heyssel, 1985-1987 (Box 74, Folder 543)
  - Johns Hopkins University, School of Hygiene and Public Health - A Five-Year Follow-Up Study of Workers Who Stopped Drinking - Carl J. Schramm, 1981-1987 (Box 74, Folder 544)
  - Johns Hopkins University, School of Hygiene and Public Health - A Five-Year Follow-Up Study of Workers Who Stopped Drinking - Carl J. Schramm, 1981-1987 (Box 75, Folder 545)
  - Johns Hopkins University, School of Hygiene and Public Health - A Five-Year Follow-Up Study of Workers Who Stopped Drinking - Carl J. Schramm, 1981-1987 (Box 75, Folder 546)
  - Johns Hopkins University, School of Hygiene and Public Health - A Five-Year Follow-Up Study of Workers Who Stopped Drinking - Carl J. Schramm, 1981-1987 (Box 75, Folder 547)
  - Johns Hopkins University, School of Hygiene and Public Health - The Development of Options for Meeting the Needs of the Functionally Dependent Elderly - Karen Davis, 1981-1985 (Box 75, Folder 548)
  - Johns Hopkins University, School of Hygiene and Public Health - The Development of Options for Meeting the Needs of the Functionally Dependent Elderly - Karen Davis, 1981-1985 (Box 75, Folder 549)
  - Johns Hopkins University, School of Hygiene and Public Health - The Development of Options for Meeting the Needs of the Functionally Dependent Elderly - Karen Davis, 1981-1985 (Box 75, Folder 550)
  - Johns Hopkins University, School of Hygiene and Public Health - The Development of Options for Meeting the Needs of the Functionally Dependent Elderly - Karen Davis, 1981-1985 (Box 75, Folder 551)
  - Johns Hopkins University, School of Hygiene and Public Health - The Development of Options for Meeting the Needs of the Functionally Dependent Elderly - Karen Davis, 1981-1985 (Box 76, Folder 552)
  - Johns Hopkins University, School of Medicine - Special Archival Development - A. McGehee Harvey, 1982-1984 (Box 76, Folder 553)
  - Johns Hopkins University, School of Medicine - Special Archival Development - A. McGehee Harvey, 1982-1984 (Box 76, Folder 554)
  - Johns Hopkins University, School of Medicine - Completion of a Review of The Commonwealth Fund's Past Activities in Medical Education and Research - A. McGehee Harvey, 1981-1986 (Box 76, Folder 555)
  - Johns Hopkins University, School of Medicine - Completion of a Review of The Commonwealth Fund's Past Activities in Medical Education and Research - A. McGehee Harvey, 1981-1986 (Box 76, Folder 556)
  - Johns Hopkins University, School of Medicine - Completion of a Review of The Commonwealth Fund's Past Activities in Medical Education and Research - A. McGehee Harvey, 1981-1986 (Box 76, Folder 557)
  - Johns Hopkins University, School of Hygiene and Public Health - Improving Ambulatory Care for Children - Barbara Starfield, 1981-1985 (Box 77, Folder 558)
  - Johns Hopkins University, School of Hygiene and Public Health - Improving Ambulatory Care for Children - Barbara Starfield, 1981-1985 (Box 77, Folder 559)
  - Joint Diseases North General Hospital - Long-Range Planning for Joint Diseases North General Hospital - Eugene L. McCabe, 1981-1984 (Box 77, Folder 560)
  - Joint Diseases North General Hospital - Long-Range Planning for Joint Diseases North General Hospital - Eugene L. McCabe, 1981-1984 (Box 77, Folder 561)
  - Joint Diseases North General Hospital - Long-Range Planning for Joint Diseases North General Hospital - Eugene L. McCabe, 1981-1984 (Box 77, Folder 562)
  - The Lab School of Washington - Development of Fund-Raising Capability - Sally L. Smith, 1982-1983 (Box 77, Folder 563)
  - The Lab School of Washington - Development of Fund-Raising Capability - Sally L. Smith, 1982-1983 (Box 77, Folder 564)
  - The Lab School of Washington - Development of Fund-Raising Capability - Sally L. Smith, 1982-1983 (Box 77, Folder 565)
  - Lenox Hill Neighborhood Association, Inc. (LHNA) - Helping Families Obtain Appropriate Care for Frail Elderly Members - David J. Stern, 1983-1985 (Box 77, Folder 566)
  - Lenox Hill Neighborhood Association, Inc. (LHNA) - Helping Families Obtain Appropriate Care for Frail Elderly Members - David J. Stern, 1983-1985 (Box 78, Folder 567)
  - Lenox Hill Neighborhood Association, Inc. (LHNA) - Helping Families Obtain Appropriate Care for Frail Elderly Members - David J. Stern, 1983-1985 (Box 78, Folder 568)
  - Lenox Hill Neighborhood Association, Inc. (LHNA) - Helping Families Obtain Appropriate Care for Frail Elderly Members - David J. Stern, 1983-1985 (Box 78, Folder 569)
  - The Library of Congress - The Congressional Research Service Seminar Program in Health Policy - Ed Mason, 1984-1988 (Box 78, Folder 570)
  - The Library of Congress - The Congressional Research Service Seminar Program in Health Policy - Ed Mason, 1984-1988 (Box 78, Folder 571)
  - Louis Harris and Associates, Inc. (LHA) - The Nature and Extent of Problems New Yorkers Face in Seeking and Using Medical Care Services - Humphrey Taylor, 1981-1983 (Box 78, Folder 572)
  - Louis Harris and Associates, Inc. (LHA) - The Nature and Extent of Problems New Yorkers Face in Seeking and Using Medical Care Services - Humphrey Taylor, 1981-1983 (Box 78, Folder 573)
  - Louis Harris and Associates, Inc. (LHA) - The Nature and Extent of Problems New Yorkers Face in Seeking and Using Medical Care Services - Humphrey Taylor, 1981-1983 (Box 78, Folder 574)
  - Louis Harris and Associates, Inc. (LHA) - The Nature and Extent of Problems New Yorkers Face in Seeking and Using Medical Care Services - Humphrey Taylor, 1981-1983 (Box 78, Folder 575)
  - Louis Harris and Associates, Inc. (LHA) - The Nature and Extent of Problems New Yorkers Face in Seeking and Using Medical Care Services - Humphrey Taylor, 1981-1983 (Box 79, Folder 576)
  - Louis Harris and Associates, Inc. (LHA) - The Nature and Extent of Problems New Yorkers Face in Seeking and Using Medical Care Services - Humphrey Taylor, 1981-1983 (Box 79, Folder 577)
  - Louis Harris and Associates, Inc. (LHA) - What New Yorkers Say About Their Health Care-1985 (Part Two) - Humphrey Taylor, 1984-1986 (Box 79, Folder 578)
  - Louis Harris and Associates, Inc. (LHA) - What New Yorkers Say About Their Health Care-1985 (Part Two) - Humphrey Taylor, 1984-1986 (Box 79, Folder 579)
  - Louis Harris and Associates, Inc. (LHA) - New Yorkers' Views on Health Issues Affecting Them - Michael Kagay, 1984-1986 (Box 79, Folder 580)
  - Louis Harris and Associates, Inc. (LHA) - New Yorkers' Views on Health Issues Affecting Them - Michael Kagay, 1984-1986 (Box 79, Folder 581)
  - Louis Harris and Associates, Inc. (LHA) - New Yorkers' Views on Health Issues Affecting Them - Michael Kagay, 1984-1986 (Box 80, Folder 582)
  - Louis Harris and Associates, Inc. (LHA) - New Yorkers' Views on Health Issues Affecting Them - Michael Kagay, 1984-1986 (Box 80, Folder 583)
  - Marine Biological Laboratory (MBL) - Planning the Marine Biological Laboratory's Centennial - Paul R. Gross, 1983-1987 (Box 80, Folder 584)
  - Marine Biological Laboratory (MBL) - Planning the Marine Biological Laboratory's Centennial - Paul R. Gross, 1983-1987 (Box 80, Folder 585)
  - Marygrove College - Career Explorations 84 - A Summer Youth Employment and Career Planning Program - Sarah C. Reese, 1984-1985 (Box 80, Folder 586)
  - Marygrove College - Career Explorations 84 - A Summer Youth Employment and Career Planning Program - Sarah C. Reese, 1984-1985 (Box 80, Folder 587)
  - Massachusetts General Hospital (MGH) - Evaluation of Breast Cancer Treatments - Oliver Cope, 1980-1985 (Box 80, Folder 588)
  - Massachusetts General Hospital (MGH) - Evaluation of Breast Cancer Treatments - Oliver Cope, 1980-1985 (Box 80, Folder 589)
  - Maternity Center Association (MCA) - Recommendations on the Future of Nurse-Midwifery Education - Ruth W. Lubic, 1981-1983 (Box 80, Folder 590)
  - Maternity Center Association (MCA) - Recommendations on the Future of Nurse-Midwifery Education - Ruth W. Lubic, 1981-1983 (Box 80, Folder 591)
  - Maternity Center Association (MCA) - Accreditation Program for Birthing Centers - Ruth Watson Lubic, 1984-1986 (Box 81, Folder 592)
  - Maternity Center Association (MCA) - Accreditation Program for Birthing Centers - Ruth Watson Lubic, 1984-1986 (Box 81, Folder 593)
  - Medicine in the Public Interest, Inc. (MPI) - Conference on Current Conceptions of "A Person" and its Implications for Medical, Social and Legal Issues - Ann Castle, 1981-1983 (Box 81, Folder 594)
  - Medicine in the Public Interest, Inc. (MPI) - Conference on Current Conceptions of "A Person" and its Implications for Medical, Social and Legal Issues - Ann Castle, 1981-1983 (Box 81, Folder 595)
  - Medicine in the Public Interest, Inc. (MPI) - Conference on Current Conceptions of "A Person" and its Implications for Medical, Social and Legal Issues - Ann Castle, 1981-1983 (Box 81, Folder 596)
  - Meharry Medical College (MMC) - Strengthening the Managerial Capacity of Meharry Medical Capacity - Richard G. Lester and Fred D. Poellnitz, 1981-1985 (Box 81, Folder 597)